y8games.info 2011-12-31

# Y8 Games - Privacy Policy - Y8Games

Privacy Policy

This Site respects your right to privacy, and we want to inform you of how we gather and handle information on each website covered by this policy.

What information does this Site collect?

When you visit this Site, we may gather the following types of information:  
a.) Personally Identifiable Data you consciously provide  
b.) Information gathered automatically like IP addresses for statistics purposes,  
c.) Non-Personally Identifiable Data you consciously provide.

To further improve the services and materials that this Site can offer and provide, we may choose to extend this site’s effectiveness for obtaining data about future users. We shall update this Privacy Policy as our process changes so that users are conscious of the progress in this area.

We do not collect email addresses for any commercial purpose. We may keep the emails of visitors, who contact us through our support email, but we keep them only for technical support purposes and we shall never sell nor divulge these email addresses to any third party,

Does this website merge personally identifiable data provided by its users with offline information about such users? If and when this Site intends to merge personally identifiable data you provided through this Website with offline information about you, this intention will be clearly stated

What security standards are in place to restrict access to personally identifiable information? This website is dedicated to safeguarding the personally identifiable data that you provide. This website is protected with various security measures such as change control procedures, physical access controls, and passwords, as applicable. We also implement other control mechanisms in an effort to help protect and conserve your personally identifiable data that you provide through this Website from being lost, misused or modified inappropriately.

Does this site knowingly gather personal data from children through this Website? This site does not knowingly gather personal data from children or through the services herewith. This website does not ask for users to provide any personal data through any page that is directed towards children. We may, however, automatically gather certain data regarding users’ visits, including areas of that are not directed towards children.We cannot always classify the age of the users who access this Website therefore we strongly encourage the parent or guardian to supervise their activities.
